London in the 1960's. Everyone had a story about the Krays.
You could walk into any pub to hear a lie or two about them.
But I was there
and I'm not careless with the truth.
They were brothers, but bound
by more than blood. They were twins as well.
Counterparts. Gangster-princes
of the city they meant to conquer.
Ron Kray was a one-man London mob.
Bloodthirsty, illogical and funny as well.
My Reggie was different.
Once in a lifetime do
you find a street fighting man like Reg.
Believe me when I say it took
a lot of love for me to hate him the way I do.
Good morning, Albie.
Good morning, sir.
Tea for two? Yeah, Albie.
Hello, boys!
How you doing? You all right? Put your cup of tea in, do you fancy it?
Yeah? No?
What's this? The old Dagenham Angila? Ought to 60 in .. what? 40 minutes or sommit like that?
Cor, it's a bit of you in that, innit?
All black and cramped and very sharp.
Yeah.
This one's really milky...for you.
Why don't you fuck off, Kray?
-Oh, I will, I will
.
Y'know, I don't want to keep you, you know, what with them ... them, y'know, rapists and murderers you got to lock away, eh nipper?
Where do you take a turd in there? Probably just hold it in, don't you?
Alright, then, have a lovely day. Cheer up.
It's nearly Christmas.
Forget about that.
Where's me driver, where's Frank?
- He can't get out of bed in the morning, Mitch.
He what?
- He ain't here, he ain't showed up. He's nah ain't here.
Alright. OK, well let's go get him then, should we? He lives on Ormsby Street, yeah?
Yeah, come and jump in.I'll give you a lift.
- Nah, you're alright, I'm going to walk.It's a lovely day for it.
Don't forget this lot. They're very important.
- I won't.
[whistles] Come on!
- I shall walk incredibly slowly!
Hi, Vera.How you doing? You good?- Yeah.- Lovely.
Rita, I was gonna knock on your door. But me mum said you left that in her kitchen.- I did!
Is that yours?
- It is! Oh, thanks ever so much!
No problem, you're welcome.
- Thanks, Reg.
Eastenders.
They won't talk to a policeman,
but they'll kiss a gangster. Ey?
Filthy, cockney bastards.
How about we clean your car for ya?
Is Frank about?
Frank!
Who are you?
- I'm Frances.Frank's sister.
Hear about, I recognize you. See, I recognize you. You was a little bit younger, then. You got grown up, didn't ya?
It happens.
What have you got there?
- A sweet.
That's not any sweet, is it? That's a Lemon Sherbert, that is. Mind if I have a crack?
Go on.- Thanks.
Ah, that's nice, innit?
You're not supposed to chew it!
- No?
How else am I supposed to get to the sherbie bit?
By being patient.
- Nah.
Being patient doesn't get you what you want, does it?
Half a minute, Reg. Be right down.
Is he in trouble?
- Yea, he is.
Will you go out with me?
I'll go easy on him if you do.
Alright, but not for that reason.
Saturday night?
Who are you talking to? You're half-dressed talking to a man in the door.
What's wrong with you, Frances?
Get back in the kitchen. Finish them dishes.
- This is yours.
Thank you.
If you oversleep again, Frank,
alright? It's back to the cheese shop.
Or the fish shop, or whatever shop it is you come from.
- Print.
Print shop.
Oh yeah? Well you'll be back to the fucking shit shop, you understand?
- Yup.
What does your sister do?
Oh, she goes to one of those, uh, Pitman colleges. Y'know? Typing? Shorthand?
- Yeah?
Well she's got a bit of class, mate. She's very elegant.
Where have you been hiding her?
She's been away.
She's a bit, umm, fragile, Reg.
Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
Hmm.- Stop here, Frank.
Four minutes. One job.
How long do you think it will take for him to figure it, Albie?
- A little bit of cat and mouse.
Nipper Read was the copper on the Krays case
and he made his presence known.
He was heavy-footed, as they say.
So I stared at the back of this geezer's head
and the whole time I'm thinking ... umm:
Give Ron Kray your sausage.
Give Ron ...
your fucking sausage.
Y'know?
I was drilling my eyes into the back of his head ...
Until I'm not even thinking it anymore.
I'm not even thinking.
I'm broadcasting it.
Until he turns around and you know what he says?
He says ...
"Hey, Ron, do you fancy my sausage?
I've got no appetite for it."
Interesting.
When my future brother in law 'interesting' said ...
- Right?
It meant he had no idea what he, or you or anyone else was talking about.
Fascinating, Ron.
Fascinating.
Ron had been sentenced to three years in prison for grievous bodily harm.
Near the end of his sentence, he was certified insane
and remanded to a mental hospital.
What was wanting was a friendly psychiatrist.
Roger, when you say you want me to raspberry this man ...
I'm not sure of your vernacular. What do you mean?
Raspberry ripple. Cripple.- You want to cripple someone.
Yup.
That's right- Why is that?
Because, doctor, I'm afraid he may not be inclined ...
to provide a favorable evaluation to my employer.
- And who is your employer?
Ronnie Kray.
Is there hope, Doctor?
Excuse me a moment.
Take your time.
Ronald Kray possesses possibly the soundest mind
I've seen in 26 years in psychiatric practice.
In my view, to keep him here would be a waste of public resources.
A lifetime's integrity down the toilet.
The Queen would survive,
but God save the rest of us.
Mr. Kray?
I hope you know what you're doing.
- Yeah, I know what I'm doing. I'm going back to London.
I'm going to take the ... take the car ...
Your brother has no real idea who or what he is. Nor does he trust his own senses.
I've never seen a man
so desperately in need of reassurance.
We all like a nice little compliment now and again, don't we?
Your brother is arbitrary, violent and a psychopath.- Alright.-
Probably paranoid schizophrenic.
What I'm trying to tell you is that he's off his fucking rocker.
It's called Stemetil. You need to give it to your brother twice a day, or there's going to be serious trouble.
Oy Frances, the car is outside.
Oh, heh, You've got glamour, Frances.
You're like an East End starlet.
East End harlot's more like it.
They're trousers, mum.
She doesn't look like a harlot.
What she's wearing doesn't matter.
When people see her with Reggie Kray,
they'll think she's a tart.
Why would you say that?
- He's a gangster, Frances. The Krays are gangsters
.
Well, I think he's sweet.- Oh, God.
And I'm going to kiss him, you hear me?
Hello.- Hello.
You look lovely
.
And so do you.
Hello. This is Big Pat. Hello, Bit Pat!
- Reggie.
How are you doing, you all right, mate? You all right?
- Nice to see you.
Big Pat's here to keep the riffraff out.
Always. *laughs*
- So how come you're letting us in, then, mate?
*laughs* Have a good night.
- Thanks.
- Thanks, mate. Cheers.
Oh hello, here's trouble. Hold the phone.
Who are you?
How you doing, big man?- All right, boss?
Are you well?
- Yeah, I'm fame...I'm fame...
Are you behaving yourself?
- Always.
I'm a teddy bear, me.
- Go easy.
If he gives you any trouble, come and speak to me. Come.
- Y'alright, mum?
Yeah, I'm good. She's good.- Hello, Reg.
Everybody here knows you.
- Yeah, well. It's my club.
You mean it's your local?
- No, I own this place. It's mine.
I've been by here ten times. I never knew it was yours
Well, you can get away with a lot in life
if you keep your mouth shut.
That's Teddy, now.
Hi, Teddy. How are you?
Good to see you. How's the family?
What?
- Those men are frightening.
No, no. They're just East End boxers. They're lovely.
I let 'em drink in here for free, y'know.
Reggie, that's Joan Collins.
- Yeah, it might be, yeah. We had
that...that...Barbara Windsor was in here the other night.
Really?
- Yeah, she comes in here quite a bit actually. She loves it.
And uh...That's my...my formula. What I like to do is mix celebrities
with a few, just a few, East End bitters.
Y'know, pugs, they love it. It's really good for business.
Would you like a seat?
Excuse me, Reg. Do you, uh, got a moment?
- No, I don't. That's it. I'm busy.
Alright?
It is important, Reg.
- This is important as well.
- Reg.
Alright, alright. Frances, would you mind
if I take care of some business just for a moment?
No, of course not.
- Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Sit with her.
What is it?
It's back here.
- What?
I'm a firm believer in the fact if you don't know,
you don't fucking know. Know what I mean?
Reggie.- How are you, Reg?
Well, I'm alright, I can't complain.
Who'd fucking listen?
What is the palaver?
- Sit down, Reg.
Sit down, please.
Alright.- You had a question about the taking of the purple art business.- Yeah.- The pill game.- Go on.
Jack here would like to explain himself.
- Go on.
Go on, Jack. Tell Reggie what you told me.
Well, Reg ...
- Yeah?
I, uh...thing is, under normal circumstances...my accountants...
Are you gonna take all fucking night, mate? Cuz
I've got things to do.
Tell him, Jack.
Go on, spit it out.
I borrowed a few quid off the top.
- Right, alright.
I swallowed a few pills on the side.- Yeah, there's a simple answer.
Things have been a bit ... tight at home
And I was...was just trying to keep the wife happy.- Trying to keep the wife happy.
Is this what you brought me in here? For this?- It's important.- This nonsense.
It's important business.
- It's important, is it?- Yeah.
You should know about this.
- Right, alright. Let's deal with this business.
Alright, tomorrow you come back to work, yeah?
and you pay back every fucking penny you owe.
Do you understand?
- I was gonna suggest that.
Good. Right. Are we done? Everybody happy?
Alright then. Can I get back to my fucking evening?
Thank you. Thank you very much, Albie.
Cheers.
Sorry for wasting your time, Jack.
- Thanks.
Thanks for coming in. Here you go, mate.
Good?
Fucking, thieving cunt. You understand...
- Get him a tissue.
*mumbles* with me? Yeah?
Next time I'll finish you off, you little slag.
Get him out of here. Go on, Fuck him off.- Fuck!
Are you fucking off. What did you say?
Don't you swear in my club.
Get him out of here right now.
Don't swear in my club, you wanker.
Now listen, there's something else.
- No, there isn't something else, alright, cuz I've got a young lady in here, and I'm entertaining.
Yeah, but this is ...
- Lookit.
See that, there?- I see it.- I'm entertaining. Alright?
So I'm gonna have an evening to myself.
This is important business.
- Can't be. My business, innit?
It's my business. I would know.
G'night, Albie.
Hello. Did I miss anything important?
No, just me.
- That? That is important.
Is it?
- Very important.
Thank you.- Thank you.
*mouths "Fuck off"*
So uh, your brother told me that you uh... you're going to college.
Right?  To...to study...to be a secretary. Is that right?
Yeah, anything to get out of the East End.
- Oh, what's so bad with the East End?
I've just got bigger dreams than pushing pram or having it with the butcher.
I just don't quite know what they are yet.
- East End is not that bad.
The center of the earth could be anywhere you like.
Even here?
- Yeah, even here.
In Bethnal Green?
- Yeah, in Bethnal Green.
Do you like being a gangster?
I'm not a gangster. I'm a club owner.
I like the money and I like the respect of being a club owner.
I'm not a gangster.
I could've been a boxer,
y'know, but then ya...hello, mate.
I'd end up looking like some sort of potato
and I wouldn't even know what day of the week it was.
This way at least I know who I am.
I also know that I've made a little bit of something of myself.
I don't owe the world anything.
So long as the world agrees with you.
I think the world will be alright.
*Winston Churchill speaking* We shall fight on the beaches
. We shall fight on the landing grounds.
We shall fight in the fields
and in the streets.
We shall fight in the hills. We shall never surrender. And if ...
Ronnie.
Ronnie, come on out.
You've got visitors, mate.
Watch your step, it's a bit wet.
Cor, you alright?
- Mmm hmm.
You must be Frances.
-Hi.
Yeah? Hello, Frances. Hello. Welcome to the family.
Well, that is a bit premature, though, isn't it?
- *laughs nervously*
Hey, you don't have a beer that I can have, do ya, Ron?
- Yeah, of course I do, help yourself.
Right. Don't mind if I have a beer, do ya?
I'll let you get to know each other.
Want a cup of tea? I just put a kettle on. Take a seat. Go on.
Sit down anywhere you like.
Ey, needs a bit of warming up. So.
What do you think?
Do you think that we look alike? Me and Reggie
?- Oh yes, certainly.
No you don't. You think that he's beautiful and I've got a face like a gorilla's ass.
*laughs* No.
- It's alright, don't worry about it. I'm used to it.
Stop doing your hair, right. Get your stuff
out of the car. Do something fucking useful.
Go on, go away.
I'm a homosexual, Frances.
wel, you know, uh, I'm a giver, not a receiver.
There is a difference.
I'm not a faggot.
I do believe that, y'know, you should not hide what you are.
Not hide what you are,
because it makes you very sad, y'know? Very sad.
Make you very unwell.
- I agree completely.- Mmm hmm.
You know me and my brother? We're gonna rule London.
The Kray's main rivals were the Richardsons of South London.
They were called the "Torture Gang '.
For the benefit of the jury ...
On whose behalf were you operating on this side of the river?
Come on, Charlie. Please, I'm begging you...
- Oh, no no no no.
You do business with the court as an entity, therefore address the court.- What?- What?
Your honor.
- Fuck!
You say 'Your Honor'. By saying Your Honor, you gain the court's attention ...
and open up a channel of communication.
A conduit.
So, we'll try again.
For the benefit of the jury: On whose behalf were you working on this side of the river?
Please, Charlie. I fucking beg you...
Order! Order in this, my court.
- Oh, fuck!
You're in Indian Country, old son.
That's what them Cockneys call south of the river, innit?
Indian Country.
Well? What you doing on my reservation without my say-so ...
filling up your canteen from my fucking watering hole?
You ain't got the balls to do that on your own son.
Who do you work for?
- I don't know what you're on about, I don't know what you're on about, Charlie.
Say it. Say the name.
Say it!
Buzz him.
Objection, Your Honor.
My client is an outstanding citizen.
Objection overruled on the grounds it's boring.
Oh well, fuck him.
Say it.
Say the Krays, you daft cunt.
No, no. No leading the witnesses!
Get out.
Alexander was then great, but not Greek.
No?
- He came from Macedonia ?.
But he loved them. Aristotle and so.
He found the Hellenistic lazy impressive.
Kristos, get more of that awful Retsina.
Charlie, we have to solve this.
You're right.
Kristos, where is my Retsina?
The Richardsons sent George Cornell
for a truce.
They said simply:
"Give peace a chance".
Frank lets do it.
Are you suddenly become brave?
- We want a ceasefire.
I'll cut you to pieces.
Let him in, he is small.
It's getting out of hand.
Charlie wants to meet.
Pig and Whistle. Neutral ground.
Only he, the two of you and Eddie.
How do we know we will be safe?
That is a matter of trust, h ??
There is always someone one ??
which starts in confidence.
If you look back, you see another guy
with a cock in his hand ...
and he wants his dick as stabbing your ass.
That you would not mind.
Dirty fagot.
You, get him out of here. Piss off.
We'll be there in an hour.
Fuck off. The door is over there.
Take creep along.
- Fuck you, asshole.
Stupid idiot.
Can I get a new egg, Charlie?
I'm done with this.
I like this but nothing, Reggie.
It's OK?. I know them and the pub.
It will be fine.
You should clean the toilet,
it smells.
It's not my fault that the housekeeper
it does not. What do you want to drink?
Never mind, they just come inside.
Can I have two Guinness?
- Moment, just replace the barrel.
The Richardsons are prevented,
So we'll take care of you.
The bartender replaces the barrel already,
but thanks.
Is it bad if I inschenk something?
What is that?
- What do you think? A weapon.
No, that's a rolling pin.
Are you sometimes Fanny Cradock?
Are you going to bake a cake for me?
Sing and watch me discharge my candles?
I come here for a gunfight
with real men.
As Colonel Custer and Geronimo.
Do you know them? Of course not.
Because you were too busy with cake baking, h ??
They're a bunch of sissies, Reg.
Really.
On the side, opzouten.
You call yourself a gangster?
A shootout is a shootout.
Just like a Western.
Idiots. What a letdown.
A goddamn waste of time.
Your brother has fled.
- He's just very disappointed.
Look, it's full of iron.
It takes a while before it comes to rest.
Charlie Richardson should we
you fully assembled rams, Reg.
Really? How kind of him. Listen.
If you see him again,
tell him I said:
Charlie can get the Fuck
and his brother also.
And those dikzak Georgie Cornell
who deals with him.
You can also get the Fuck.
And the rest of it,
What do you think of that?
Like what?
Do you mind if I fight back?
- Can you handle it then?
It's more for my own pride.
I warn you that I do not fight fair.
That's why I brought it.
Before we begin, I want to tell a joke.
You will find this amazing.
A man with paranoid schizophrenia
comes into a bar ...
Assholes.
They had no chance against my handsome Reggie.
A gang war seemed a certainty.
- Damn it, Ron.
But during the World Cup final,
interfered with Scotland Yard also undertaken.
There's Ball,
which runs from the lungs to the body.
Come on, idiots.
Police, stay where you are.
- Come on, not today. Why not a goal?
Wait.
It is a goal.
Charlie Richardson got 25 years in prison
fraud, extortion and assault.
London was an open city
and the Krays seized their chance.
Glad you could come, Mr. De Faye.
Mr. Payne.
I'm not easily ge? Intrigued,
but your message ...
was intriguing.
Sit down.
This is the Kray twins.
Ronald and Reginald.
I've heard of them.
- They are useful friends.
What is this about, Mr. Payne?
- A casino in Knightsbridge, Esmeralda's Barn.
I do not know it.
- Really?
You will be surprised that you have ?24,000
to have earned over the past three months.
My friends and I would like to buy it.
The contract is ready to sign.
In order to rule over London,
intelligence and intimidation was necessary.
It's not for sale.
In the future this will probably
not go so polite.
The trick was to create a quiet certainty? Run.
That violence is always an option, if needed ...
, and the like will be used.
Leslie Payne was a swindler and fixer.
Reggie Payne found useful,
but Ron was suspicious.
He was afraid that his scam
did not fit the life of a gangster.
Consider Las Vegas.
It is legal and is run by the mafia.
London is the same soon.
Havana is now gone, the mob is coming.
Meyer Lansky has already made inquiries.
- Meyer Lansky?
The real Meyer Lansky?
Meyer Lansky.
Americans want our silence?
- They will not have to work.
They do not want war, Ron.
They are businessmen.
Maybe I do want war.
They want to know who the new
promising local company is.
They colonize London by that company
finance and roll out a franchise.
Prove to the Americans,
the Krays the only gang in the city.
Interestingly though.
The world can be ours.
- Payne.
You say quite often "us".
You say 'us' and 'we' tell you much.
Is that right?
Is your last name sometimes Kray?
You can keep the beautiful things, Ron.
I'll take the rest.
I'd like to believe that.
Reggie, I think it's a bad idea.
I think we bastards from the mafia
should meet at the airport.
We pick them up, murder them
and send them in their own luggage home.
Now that's a plan.
I am pleased with this meeting.
Mr. Lansky is ge Interested
in the Colony Sporting Club.
His casino people are there now.
Mr. Lansky would like to know,
we have a casino.
Really? Your own casino?
Las Vegas is our property.
But here's the Atlantic
us in the way.
So Mr. Lansky can be owned
not physically secure.
Both against outsiders as the police.
He thinks the Kray family can help.
London is the Las Vegas of Europe.
We need someone who does our business
and fighting for us.
We can provide you security,
but we do not want to work for you.
We prefer to cooperate.
What Reggie to say ...
- That he knows best. He said the net.
We are on your site.
Mr. Lansky would like best about discussi? Run.
He sends this as a gesture of good will.
As a taster. Open it, please.
In the second case are matters
I have to handle myself.
Bonds. Free money.
$ 100,000 in bonds
stolen from a bank in Montreal.
We can not lose in North America.
It is $ 100,000.
Can you handle that?
We can to do that.
Really? Beautiful.
Boys who commit robberies get 20%.
We share the rest 60/40.
If this goes well, Reggie,
I lie still two million in bonds.
Does that sound as if you stay in our neighborhood?
50/50, friend.
I like you, Reggie.
50/50, agreed.
I am pleased that we have closed a deal.
This feels good.
Come to Philadelphia ...
and if you see something you like,
You can get that from us.
An Italian girl
or spaghetti with meatball.
I prefer boys.
Sorry, I did not hear you.
I said I'd rather have boys.
Ideally Italians.
Sometimes Greeks, but I'm not biased.
I have actually ever had a Negro.
And someone from Tahiti, which I in the creases
have worked. I made him real pain.
You have guts you relent.
You really have balls.
You know what I say?
Bravos and cheers. Am I right or not?
On balls, cheers.
Well done.
- Cheers.
You do not understand.
He's not what you think.
He is very sweet
and it is exciting to be with him.
I do not have such a boring life if you do.
I have a boring life,
because I sacrificed it for you.
Frankie, you deprive me of my breath.
You can have mine.
You're a joke dress.
Sit in the car.
Hurry up.
Esmeralda's Barn was very profitable.
?2,000 pure profit per week.
We could just enjoy it.
That casino was all for Reggie.
He had finally crossed the border
between the old East End and Golden West.
He was a celebrity.
As long as their health permitted,
the rich were happy with gangsters.
Aristocrats and criminals
have much in common.
Both are selfish,
bored quickly ...
and have access to money,
where they have never worked honestly for.
The best?
Both of them do not care about morality of the rules.
Put in a roulette wheel at
and you have the key to success.
Ron was the odd man out.
Through his pills he was stable,
but he would never recover.
He did not like the club life ...
and he longed for Reggie
and the dark side of the gangster life.
As soon as you turn your back ...
life playing dirty games.
We were not together at Christmas that year.
There was an old warrant against Reggie.
He appealed for the last six months
his sentence, but this was rejected.
He had to morning vomit.
My real life was about to begin at the point.
See you later.
Until later, Reg.
- Bye.
Frank.
Would you watch your sister when I'm gone?
- I will, Reg.
Well done.
Hurry up, Kray.
Stop on the line.
You are nothing.
Beat him.
Beat him up.
Leave him alone, Gibbsy.
- Kill him, Reggie .
Shut up, everyone.
Come on, Reg.
- Do not do this .
You're not so tough anymore, h ??
Make that bastard off.
You are nothing.
Nothing.
- Stop, please.
That's better, Reggie.
A little respect can not hurt?
Stop.
I have turned bigger turds.
Water, please.
- You want some water?
Look at that, gentlemen.
He begs for water.
What do you now
the famous Reggie Kray?
Begging for water.
What has become of him?
Please, Reg. Not spill.
You're a little shaky, do not you?
Here.
Well done.
There he is.
Reggie Kray, begging for water.
Hello, Frances.
Hi, Ron.
- I've seen Reg today.
He says hello
and says he still should not visit.
Did he say why?
- No.
Did you know that it is possible
to become a ghost while you're still alive?
Do you think?
You're talking about is?
No, listen.
- No, what?
Just listen, please.
Casinos are required by law
to pay out prizes right away.
Therefore, the gamblers have their debts
immediately repay. It's simple.
I heard you,
but that's your problem and not mine.
My problem is that I want ?50,000.
Now you start again about ?50,000
to go to Nigeria.
It is not just to go to Nigeria.
I want to start a business.
I want a city for children
building in Nigeria.
Near Enugu.
- Enugu, yes.
I said Enugu.
You do not know anything, either, Payne?
Did you know that "Enugu"
the African word for 'Utopia' is?
No.
- Not so.
Did you know that 'Utopia'
the Greek word for 'nowhere' is?
With ?50,000 can I 'somewhere' out of it.
I can make a spot of there
where people laugh at me and dancing children.
I laugh so much for you, Ron.
I do that, when you tell me
I going to get ?50,000.
I'm telling you, take it out of the casino.
I can not do that.
- Get it out of the casino, asshole.
Do not mess with a legal, profitable business.
- I am not a banker.
I am not a banker.
- Brilliant, that's much better.
This is a man who wants to build a city.
- Not threaten me, asshole.
do not you dare
to speak to me, asshole.
Reggie is not there. He is gone.
You work for me, Ron Kray.
So you go to the bank
and takes anywhere from ?50,000.
I'll go to the bank
and see what I can do.
I might work for you, Ron,
but I'm not afraid of you.
Then you are also stupid,
for that you have to be.
If my brother had not vouch for you,
you were dead.
What happened?
What are you doing here?
Said Ronnie not want you to stay away?
I missed you.
Frankie, I do not want me here like this.
Do you understand?
Who did that?
- What?
Your face.
Was it another inmate?
No, it was a jailer.
Have you given them?
- No.
If I'm free, I'll talk to the prime minister.
Who listens well.
Frankie, it's the prison.
That's just the way.
The laws of the jungle apply here.
But I'm a big boy
and can take care of myself. I'm pretty soon.
Look at that big guy there.
With that big hat.
We call him for a reason 'sissy'.
I do not want this life.
Wait for you while you're stuck.
- I know that.
Frankie, it will not happen again.
How do you know that?
- Because I know.
Because I promise you
that it will not happen again.
I know how you can know for sure.
- Tell.
You can go on the right path.
Be the owner of a casino or club.
Do you like it.
Forget the rest.
It really is that simple for you, h ??
"Get on the right path."
Life is not always
as we want, sweetheart.
Life has other plans.
So that way it is.
I love you.
I've never loved anyone,
but I love you, Reggie.
I love you too.
Do you think it can protect people?
- What?
Love.
I think he's right. He has something.
You know what I think it is?
His hips.
I want to enjoy blowing on the trumpet.
Are you horny, Ron?
That's right.
Do it.
- I will. I want to blow the trumpet.
I am going to do it.
All right, Ron. Bladder but tasty.
Stop it.
Hey?
- Hello, Ron.
You know when I plan
to die?
When, Ron?
If the latest deal is closed.
Encourage him not to damn it.
Look at you now rich people sit down.
I may not be so good,
but a good gangster?
I like to claim that title.
How many titles can you claim?
Superficial lazy.
It is thus thrown into your lap.
It's disgusting, really.
A little magic then, which do you like.
Every child loves magic.
You know that there are three times the letter 'K'
in the word "cooking" occurs.
But how many K's ...
are there in the word "asshole"?
Your ankle.
You're free.
Why are you throwing stones at the window?
- They are not stones but Lemon sherberts.
Please.
Good catch.
Why do not you call it?
- By your mother.
The idea that your mother
the door would open, is creepy.
They will tackle me hard
to have been where I am.
You mean prison?
- Exactly. You look beautiful.
You too.
I know it's late,
but I got your Christmas present here.
Should I throw it up?
- No.
Should I deliver it?
I do not by that door.
Good.
Hussy.
Careful.
Little late, is not it?
Your flowers.
- Thank you.
And...
your Christmas present.
Sorry it's so late.
Open it.
Frances Shea, will you marry me?
We are living free and legal?
I swear.
Yes, Reggie Kray, I will marry you.
Which was not mine.
Brutal.
If so.
Show me your ass, that is.
- You do not listen.
I only say that the crime
still is a business.
There is a PR department needed
and we have Joseph Goebbels.
Is he fat?
You can read lips.
What he says, Les?
He talks to me
about hoops or domes?
That's weird.
You're not happy.
You will see it.
Nice is not it?
He looks good, Ron.
He has grown some muscle.
He will be upset.
Did I miss something?
Is not Friday night?
- I tried to tell you.
But it's Friday?
You did not think it was so bad.
It's because of Ron. He has ruined the company.
He has made a financial wreck it.
And the company will go bankrupt
if we have to pay taxes.
What is he saying?
You paid no tax, the idiot.
We go.
This morning we act out, understand?
How rude.
Where are you going?
- This is criminal.
There's my handsome brother, Reggie.
A toast to my handsome brother.
Finally home, like Agamemnon's return
to Ithaca.
And beautiful Frances, where were you?
It's like being resurrected from the dead.
What are you doing?
What kind of game do you play?
I do not play games, you can.
You do not even greet me.
We do not drink and you just go away.
- All right. Hi, Ron. Thanks.
Fuck you.
- Why are you yelling?
You had the world at your feet ...
but you could not deal with it,
So did you just fucked up.
You were gone.
I was stuck.
- I had to make do with what I had.
Do you go for Ron and Reg?
To bet?
Reginald. He does not lose
in front of his girlfriend.
You had everything.
- Jou not.
Unbelievable. I'll handle this off.
It'll be fine.
He can handle it, it's a big boy.
We're talking about business.
We are talking about gangsters, because we are.
So you can fuck off.
Get out.
- Do not.
Someday you by your terrible life
be engulfed, Ron Kray.
You should know.
I've heard all the horror stories.
Your mother gave us damaged goods, h ??
And you're damaged, right?
Go to the car.
You never talk anymore at Frances.
For example, is that, Frances. Blood is thicker than water.
I've been with Reggie together since the womb.
Shut up, Ron.
Frances offer your apologies.
All right, Frances.
I'm sorry, okay?
Very. The club is rather empty.
A bit like you.
There is not much in,
outside the dick of my brother.
You are a disgrace.
You hit me.
No, Ron.
Now you have done it, asshole.
Asshole.
Not the bottle.
Not my balls.
Idiot.
Please go away, darling.
Dirty Bastard.
Give me that.
You should not sit on someone's balls.
What are you doing?
No, Ron. That is a bottle.
I pull them apart.
- No, stay seated.
It's family.
Give them space.
Beat him down.
I told you.
- It's enough like this.
No.
Enough, Reg.
You do not understand.
You do not understand me.
- Because I do not want to understand, Ron.
I just wanted ...
- It is useless to explain.
It's hopeless. Help me up.
It was painful.
What are you doing? Damn it, Ron.
What I'm trying to tell you is simple.
Listen to me.
I am very ...
fragile, ok ??
Fragile, understood.
Fragile.
- I understand.
Hurry up.
I'm not myself, do you?
This is not me, is it?
So we are not.
I am very sorry.
- It is well.
Are you done?
Is she gone?
Yes, she's gone.
I would love her.
Thanks, Ron.
There she is.
- I see her.
Ok ?, stop here.
She'll be mad at me.
Go ahead.
Frankie. Frank.
Sorry.
Can I talk to you?
- I do not care if you forget me.
Do not say that.
- It's true.
You're kidding me.
- Do not tell me what I mean. I know what I mean.
Come on, Frances.
Can we start over?
From the beginning.
We can leave out all the bad ...
and everything is tightly.
And then Ron?
- What about Ron?
He is not exactly a good thing, do you?
- But he's not really bad.
He was horrible to me yesterday.
- That he was, but that's Ron.
If he does not take his pills, he does.
He is a nightmare.
He is not always so.
He has a heart of gold.
He loves you, he thinks you're wonderful.
When you left, he was devastated.
He said: "Where did she go?"
I said, "She's gone."
Go after, you should keep her.
You're here to stay, he's right.
Tell her I'm sorry.
He regrets, and me too.
Sorry all.
But you know what?
It sometimes just happens.
Families are stupid, right?
They ruzi? N and make amends.
And eventually they stay together
because they love each other.
That's what they do.
Do not say I remember you,
because that will not happen.
I think the last six months of life to you.
I come out and the club's a mess ...
Sorry.
OK?.
It was time for the Krays to the secret
entering history of the 60's.
How absurd it seems ...
it became Ron's dream in which he
"builds n utopian city in Nigeria.
Some are born to be Ronnie Kray ...
and some to be Ronnie Krays confidant.
Lord Boothby was a distinguished member
House of Lords.
Ronnie.
- Yes?
I regret that I must decline.
Nigeria is simply too far away ...
and I'm no relationship with anything
I can not personally verify.
Sorry.
He's really nice, is not it?
I assume you want ice and a slice, sir?
Ice and a slice.
Please teddy bear.
And like a little fast.
Do you know where I heard
that lemons are particularly tasty and fresh?
No. True?
In Enugu in Nigeria.
You're good you? Informed, Teddy.
Very good you? Informed.
Ad fundum.
Do you like the ad fundum, Teddy?
Boothby hit down the offer,
but the friendship was formed.
And Perrin was a quick guest
in one apartment of Ron.
The ripple would spread far and wide.
Call me later, Tom.
Harry, all alone?
It is not necessary,
there is plenty of fruit on the tree.
Tom, not in the House of Commons tonight?
Yes.
Look at me, asshole.
Yes?
Now look at him.
Look at me, damn it.
Look at me.
Good heavens, that's Bob Boothby.
Yes, Prime Minister.
That's an orgy.
They will find it difficult to explain this.
Here.
Is that Tom Driberg?
Yes, sir.
There is no moral advantage for my party
if my party also is involved.
Here it is what penibeler.
Where these pictures were taken?
Cazenove Road in Hackney.
What were they doing in Hackney?
- That's where it gets awkward.
I thought the orgy was awkward,
but it gets worse?
We had two brothers, gangsters, under guard.
The Krays.
The photos were taken in the apartment of Ron Kray.
The orgy aside, we follow fraud
and criminal practices.
And the American mafia
There also might be involved.
London underworld had reached its peak.
Threatened a scandal.
The election is over ten weeks.
They will both sides
Voting out the parliament.
What exactly do you do about it?
Nothing, apparently.
Is that Italian?
I do not know.
Is it some Daimler?
No, that's not it.
What do you want for Christmas?
I do not know. You have to give me anything.
You have to give me a gift.
That is ridiculous.
Give you nothing for Christmas?
Surprise me then.
- I'll give you a sack of coal.
I think I'll give you a sack of coal.
Lucky.
And then?
What is it?
For Christmas.
For me?
This is my club.
Is that right?
- Yes.
West End, a touch of class.
This is our chance to get out of here.
It's snowing.
Away.
What I wanted for Christmas?
My Reggie, free and orderly.
But Ron Reggie wanted to be back as well.
He longed for his gangster twins.
But Reggie chose the "Hide-a-way."
The owner was Hew McCowan,
son of a baronet.
Although he was not normally ge? intimidated
by the working class ...
he agreed,
to sell half of the club.
Reggie knew he rest
would get in due course.
An unfair deal for an honest life.
Ron was terrified
Reggie would leave him behind.
He sent Teddy to make the deal broke.
I have talked to Reggie ...
I can not look at you, otherwise I'm lost.
I have an appointment with Reggie ...
- This tastes nasty.
I signed a contract.
I have a contract with Reggie, ask him.
Rubbish.
- Please.
I have customers.
On the side. Come on.
I have customers, gentlemen, please.
I have talked to Reggie.
We do not work for Reggie.
We work for Ronnie.
Ron almost got what he wanted.
McCowan waived the deal,
but also called the police.
Reggie and Ron were both indicted
for extortion.
I tell you, the police will come for me.
I am innocent.
Even if it is ...
What?
You go back to jail.
You promised me something.
That still applies.
I am innocent, damn it.
Sorry, I curse against you.
I want you to marry me.
Please.
If you're innocent and acquitted,
I'll marry you.
If you're guilty, I want to see you again.
- Why do you say that?
Frankie, which ...
Frankie, really.
Strangely enough, it was Lord Boothby
who saved.
His wild excesses
had not gone unnoticed.
I have finally found her.
She was sent to the right places.
Say: "Enugu".
Enugu.
The photo was taken in Boothby's flat
in the newspapers go.
Along with the story of sexual misconduct ...
between a gangster and one member of the House of Lords.
The problem is that, unfortunately ...
This time all true.
The truth does not interest me, Harold.
Except that, the greater the truth ...
the greater the scandal.
The election was imminent.
Therefore asked the Prime Minister Arnold Goodman
to solve the problem.
Give me Cecil King of the Sunday Mirror.
The great and the good
took care of the concealment.
When defending the Krays
Boothby wanted to testify ...
the commitment was clear.
The government had dropped its case ...
or face the consequences.
This allows the Krays were the elusive
of the London underworld.
New information suggests the witness
the prosecutor, Mr. McCowan, in a bad light.
The case has been dismissed.
That evening celebrated the Krays
their victory in club McCown.
Reggie had the same afternoon
The "Hide-a-way" bought.
With discount.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
I want the difference between you and me.
The difference?
OK?.
What you say about that.
- I grew up poor on ...
just like you.
As a boy I boxed, just like you.
But it did not change me into a thief.
But it's you
turned into a cop, right?
Yes.
It changed you into someone
indicating his own people.
You know, the difference between us ...
beyond the obvious ...
I work for myself.
Do you ...
You work for them.
I can explain.
This is Scotland Yard.
And this research is stopped immediately.
But we can get so much more ...
- Your investigation into the Krays stops immediately.
She's wearing black.
Yes I know. She misunderstood.
She thought it was a funeral.
She wears black, that stupid bitch.
- I know. Do not let them get to you.
Wait till you see her daughter,
she looks amazing in white.
What do you see?
I see myself.
I see what I could be.
Do you know.
If I was not so scared.
- You're not afraid of anything.
Right.
Well, so much for myself.
And you.
What is she doing?
You know what they'll say.
Take a deep breath.
Why are not you inside?
- Are you really sure you want to do this?
Mom, do not start again.
- It's all right, Frank.
I love him.
Love.
Do you know what love is, Frances?
I know it does not answer anything.
But love is a witness.
Reggie sees me.
And I see him.
Who are you to reject it?
I'm your mother.
East End style, Frances.
That's you.
Thank you.
Ron, you should see her.
She looks beautiful.
Enjoy it.
Merciful God ...
accept our prayers for Frances and Reginald ...
that they may acquire the harvest of the Spirit ...
and reflect your glory
in our Lord Jesus Christ.
Amen.
Sing, damn it.
We went to Greece for our honeymoon.
The Parthenon was already 2,400 years.
Reggie's promise to remain honest
held two weeks stand.
Two Aces ...
New Mill ...
Gigi Club ...
not to mention Ronnie Scott's.
And this is the catch in Hamburg.
The kettles boiling.
It is tea.
We started near Marble Arch in West London.
But both we missed East End.
That's why we took an empty apartment
in Rons Cedra Court.
Just like everything else in our lives
for it would be temporary.
Not very smart.
Rons parties kept me awake at night.
And club life kept Reggie
until the late hours away.
He enjoyed it anyway 'n be gangster.
- We heard that you were last in the Regency.
You waved a gun.
The brothers Barry kept me going on inside.
They said I was drunk.
That was you.
You were drunk.
And waved a gun.
No.
You know that here was not gone.
Not true?
You know that you were there on the balls.
I made it more interesting for people.
More interesting.
Please.
You do not do that again, do you?
No, sir.
Brave boy.
Damn.
Stand up.
This is so nice of you.
Strange, is not it?
- Indeed.
Hey.
Is that OK??
- No.
No, Frances, that's not good enough.
Sit down with Mr. Kray,
I'll figure it out.
OK?.
She can not even
put a decent cup of tea.
Poor Reggie.
It was a good attempt.
She's like a fool in that dress.
You would not pick her
as she lay in the gutter.
Poor Reggie.
Well ...
I throw this away.
I left without saying goodbye.
A sad victory.
I would never be good enough for their Reggie.
He was also Nippers Reggie.
Read did not rest
when he saw my husband ?? once a day.
I had to settle for the same.
Wherever you go,
do not stop until you reach the sea.
But we all need something.
What I had in common with Ron
the pills were to get through the day.
Sleeping pills sometimes helped,
other pills helped other times.
They were like a friend without judgment ...
, and only wanted to be loved
in return.
Mother's little helpers.
Their name was appropriate.
Do not go too fast.
We're going far too fast.
We walk on the grass.
Ok ?, we're almost there.
OK?.
- A little further?
Ready? All done?
- Yes.
Oh my God.
Do you like it?
Yes, what is it kind?
What's it called?
It is a Triumph. A Triumph Spitfire.
- Can I be in it?
Of course, it's yours.
Happy Birthday. Please.
Congratulations, Frances.
- Thank you.
Would you take a ride with me?
I can do that.
Now?
- Not today.
Why not?
I can not today.
But I can tomorrow.
- OK?.
Sorry.
Kray.
There's an inherent threat
in that one syllable.
It is the only word
what some people need to hear.
What do you mean by 'the only word?
You're just Ford.
Or Shell.
Or Woolworth's.
Woolworth's.
Yes, that's very interesting.
I'm just saying Kray is a brand ...
and an established reputation
less maintenance, use less violence.
The people comply.
Clubs have been asking for our protection
Before we get there.
That's true. They do that.
Then we need them also to indicate less justified.
He is right.
That makes sense.
You know what I like?
Occasionally I like reprimanding nice.
Occasionally throw someone on the cobblestones.
Whats wrong with that?
I think you can do better, Ron.
It keeps you out of jail.
We are not getting any younger.
You should leave this all behind you, you know?
You have to look to the future,
you and your beautiful young woman.
Asshole.
I am warning you.
This is a company. That is a fact.
Are you okay? Can you see?
I do not work for you. Stupid bastard.
Was excessive.
I do not like him. I do not trust him.
He talks too much, ask too many questions.
I want him dead.
Leslie Payne is our business partner,
and you want him dead.
You've taken your pills?
- Fuck your pills.
Fuck Payne,
the bastard with his damn briefcase.
It does not care what's in there,
I want to know what happens there.
He knows too many things.
Things about us.
He knows too much about us.
He knows too much about us?
Albie, you do know things about us?
He knows things ...
Ron about me and about the company ...
you know about the payments.
You know that we collect bonds.
You know we bribe juries
so they see us as benevolent.
Yes.
You know, that's a surprise.
Jack, my friend, do you know anything about fraud?
Whatever.
Do you know anything about how to bribe the police
every last Thursday of the month.
Do you know?
- Yes of course.
What a surprise, say.
Why do we murder Jack now?
Or Albie? All of them.
I'll kill you and you to me,
then we're both dead.
This is a genius idea.
Listen to yourself, Ron.
You're awfully disturbed.
People who live in glass houses
should not throw stones.
Did you know I'd never drunk gin
before I came here?
Soon you sing 'God save the Queen' yet.
What did you want to talk to me, Mr. Bruno?
Doing very well,
we are very happy on our side of the sea.
Which is good. We are also very happy.
OK?.
Cheers.
Do you realize that I asked to speak to you alone?
You see, in our line of work ...
it is not good to be famous.
Anonymity is the goal.
It is Mr. Lansky, Reg.
He sees a lot of potential in you.
But your brother Ron sees limitations.
Maybe ...
they must meet.
He must come for a chat.
- A talk?
You guys are hilarious.
Have you ever heard of the Gallo brothers?
From Brooklyn?
It was a similar situation.
You see, Ron is your Joey.
And in both cases, it will not end properly.
What exactly do you ask of me, Mr. Bruno?
I ask you to do something about Ron.
I can not do that.
He is my brother.
Good.
I can not do anything.
I'm not done with you.
Mr. Kray provides this warehouse.
- If you remember ?? n times Kray says ...
I will beat you, understand?
I have an agreement with Mr. Kray.
- I did not ask you.
I asked if you understood me.
The Richardson gang was gone.
But George Cornell had crossed the river
to demand their 't protection money.
I fucking warned you.
Ron's reply would give him his place
in delivering the gangster legend.
Is this English breakfast tea?
- You can tell by your face what you think.
Beautiful box.
- It is not an English breakfast tea, no.
There are pheromones in.
It is musky.
The best they make nowadays.
Really delicious, is not it?
I'm glad you like it.
- It does.
My mother will be very happy.
Got this from the old warehouse?
Do not say anything, it's good.
Say hello to Mrs. Kray me.
- Thank you.
And the other issue.
What issue?
That?
Well...
Do not you think
that I will pay it, do you?
You can not handle it yourself?
I pay you for protection, Ron.
What is your point?
Nothing ...
- You said it.
You come here with that damn nose.
And your tea.
Your exotic teas.
Right? And you say this.
I did not do my job.
I did not mean it like that.
- That you did.
No, I ...
I'll tell you what.
This question of yours ...
I will for you to handle. OK??
Go along with Teddy
and bring me 2000 pounds, ok ??
In return, I promise
I let George Cornell murder.
Well?
I did not ...
- Good?
I said nothing about murder, Ron.
- You did damn well.
You meant it.
Look at me, you meant it with your eyes.
Look at your eyes.
I see it in your eyes.
Are you threatening me?
- No.
For it is dead in your eyes
and you threaten me.
He threatening me?
- It's hard to say, Ron.
I'll pay it.
- What are you doing?
- Sure. A deal is a deal.
It's done so.
It is done. It's good.
Teddy, take him.
Thank you.
Very kind of you.
Thanks for the tea.
This is a good deal.
Blind Beggar
How do I look?
Damn deadly.
You want me to go in with it?
Inside.
Come on.
You stay in the car.
Is there anything I should know?
Look who's here.
Jesus.
Now do not laugh, h ??
Damn, that's sick.
Boss, damn ...
On the ground.
Shut up.
What are you looking at?
You've seen nothing.
That's Ronnie Kray, right?
Damn.
Reggie.
Are you crazy?
The Blind Beggar? Cornell?
It is on the radio.
Reggie.
Hi Mom.
Please.
- Thank you.
Look at you now agree.
Look how handsome you are.
I grab a cup of tea.
- Thanks, Mom.
Albie?
- No, thank you, Violet.
You look good, Reg.
How many witnesses?
- It was a quiet evening.
Seven.
- Seven?
Albert Woods was at Cornell.
And a few regular customers.
I do not know them.
And the barmaid, the blonde with the big eyes.
Damn.
And you bring it here, to your mother?
Do not bother, it happened.
What are we going to do now?
'We'?
Where's the gun?
Here, Reg.
Please.
Want a piece of cake?
That would be nice. Yes.
Thanks, Mom.
Yes, it is tasty.
- Thanks.
They've seen you in those clothes, right?
Yes.
- Where's his jacket?
Which you need to burn.
The weapons we have to dump into the river.
Go now.
You're unbelievable.
Albie. We have to find out
who in the caf? sat.
Approach them and uncover
what they told the police.
It has to be negated.
Send Pat and Bender.
That bartender I know anyway?
- Yes.
Bring her to me.
I'll talk to her.
Go ahead.
Where is everyone going?
Mom, it's late.
I did not want them to bother you.
You should go to sleep so.
Shall I take you home? Come on.
No need, I'm home.
I have the bed made up for him.
He is not well.
He has a fever.
He will remain here tonight.
Teddy, you want to stay with him?
That would be nice. Thank you, Violet.
What he has done ...
He's your brother.
Yes.
Here are your pills.
You need to take them.
I have to go.
The boys are still at work ...
and I have to clean up.
I must say good night.
- Good night.
Teddy, would you do us a favor?
When he takes off his pants tonight ...
and his shirt,
make sure you burn them.
Please contact me.
Good guy.
Good evening.
He's nice, is not it?
Even Scotland Yard
murder on the street could not ignore.
Nipper again worked on the case.
Gentlemen, your attention please.
You have been told
we carry out an important research ...
in a serious accusation of corruption.
In fact, we go after the Krays.
Anyone can come to me with any objections.
See that post there?
That is known as one safety tip
during the war.
If you could walk to the post ...
did you know you could reach the bunker
Before the bombs would fall.
One evening were Ron and I looked and there.
We saw Stanton House fly into pieces.
They were still inside.
It's a miracle you're alive.
Yes, especially Ron.
Every time there are problems
he drags them behind him.
He has enough problems
if the stories are true.
I heard it on the street, Reggie.
My own family,
and you did not tell me.
I did not want you to worry.
I'm not worried about Ron.
What are you going to do about it?
I do not let him go to prison.
- Why not?
Why not? Because he's my brother.
Even in prison he is still your brother.
- No.
No, Frances, he belongs here with us.
He belongs to you, me and his family.
This is his home.
I care for him as he is free.
So it is.
In prison you can take care of him.
And he does not belong here, you know.
Right.
You just do not understand.
Yes.
- No, you're not.
You once said that your world was not guilty.
You're Ron also not guilty.
My loyalty to my brother,
is my measure, you understand?
And your loyalty to me?
Is not that standard?
What could be wrong with your eyes?
Do you use something?
Did you take something, Frances?
Take your pills again?
Let's see.
No, stop it.
- Hey, look at that.
Good God, Frances, how much is that thinking?
No wonder you do not understand.
You're addicted to pills.
That you've made of me.
- What? A pill swallower?
Let's be clear about what you say.
If we want to be free, we need to be alone?
Great, Frances.
I agree with that.
Talk to the barmaid.
Tell her, as they draw the suspects,
she points to Ron and said, "That's him."
"That's the guy who did it."
OK??
Where are you going?
- Home.
And my mother?
Which can be stolen.
Take your time.
- No.
The man who shot Cornell is not here.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
Can somebody take me home?
Mrs.
I swear.
I smelled something but did not know what it was.
But I caught a glimpse of the court.
The smell came from him.
Am I right or not?
Am I wrong, Reg?
It shows that you are a dog
a bad name can give ...
but when that hot dog Kray,
He can bite back. Well done, Ron.
Justice is satisfied.
Welcome home.
On discipline.
Take one, Vi.
- No.
Give her the pink biscuits.
Somebody has to eat them.
What did you say to her?
I told her to think of her children.
I wish I could disappear.
Good luck with that, Frances.
Damn luck with that.
It is a heavy downpour.
What is she doing?
It amazes me that some people ...
still survive today.
See you later, Albie.
Are you okay?
- Yes, go.
Everything good? He's stuck?
Help me.
Help you?
What are you doing?
Help me to put on the cap.
- I do not know if I can help you.
Please, he's still so broken.
I can not, I'm a club owner.
I can pick out a beautiful model
and a beautiful color ...
but I can not help you.
I'm not a mechanic.
I'm more of a gangster.
Not true?
Please, help me.
- Please, help me?
Please.
Please, Reggie.
Ok ?, I'll help you.
How about that?
This seems pretty messed up, right?
By the way ...
You look awful.
What are you doing?
Reggie, stop it. Stop.
Reggie.
Which stop?
Do not do it please.
Please stop.
Please. No.
Stop.
Life goes on without me.
Where are you going?
I leave Reggie.
That is a pity that it will fall hard.
Please go to the side, Ron.
Unless you'd prefer me to stay.
You go, boys.
I will help you with your bags?
No thanks.
- Come on, do not be stupid.
See how great I am compared to you.
Come on.
You know, Frances, sometimes you achieve greatness ...
Really, you have a small part
cut yourself ...
How much does it well,
to grow and move forward.
It takes courage and I admire that.
In fact, I think
you just leave on time.
Do you think?
- Yes.
There are so many people
who know a lot about us.
Not you, of course.
Most people hate us.
Sooner or later someone will talk
and the game will be over.
That would not be so bad, does it?
I think God but what
by should condone, do not you think?
Yes, God does probably.
He's gone too far.
So we are not educated.
I have to go.
Yes of course.
Listen, Frances,
we both love him.
We have both tried.
We just have to see what happens,
when we get there.
True?
In heaven.
Goodbye, Ron.
Goodbye, Frances.
Listen...
I've always liked you.
Really, Frances.
Because you have the ability
to look into the future.
You can do that. The same goes for me.
Bye.
Hello, Reggie.
How are you?
All right, Frank?
Long time no see.
- I'm on the right path.
Really? How nice.
Very nice.
What can I do for you?
Frances is there?
I'm already weeks before her parents' home.
They did not say that she was left ...
So I stood there like a fool under her window.
She's here.
- I know.
Reggie, I ...
- What?
I have not seen her for so long.
She is sensitive.
- Right.
Go call Frances.
I had to come here. Go get her.
Reggie, I do not want you to see her.
- Do not go screwing around.
Frances, go inward. What are you doing?
- Do not worry. Hello, Reggie.
Hello, Frances.
Do you have a minute?
Then we can talk.
It's OK?.
- Sure?
Go put in tea.
Frankie, come home.
I am home.
Until I find another place, at least.
I can not live with my mother.
What can I do to your mind
to let it change?
You can not.
I've changed my mind about one thing ??.
- And that is?
I want that you will always remember me.
I existed and I once walked beside you.
- What are you talking about?
Frankie, come on.
I thought we'd have children.
Why?
So you can use them to threaten me?
No.
Because I still love you.
You just say out of loyalty
for something that did not exist.
Not true. Loving you is the only
that makes me not collapse.
I wish we could live a life
outside the one we are destined for.
But you're a gangster and you love it.
No, Frances, listen.
Let me pain
I have caused to make up, please.
Please.
Let me take you anywhere you go.
Somewhere?
- Does not matter where. What you want.
Just us two, so we can be together.
It's like a second honeymoon.
Or not.
As long as you know that I can change.
And I've changed.
I only say that the center of the world
could be anywhere.
Everywhere.
Ibiza.
- What?
Ibiza. Let's go there.
I think the word so beautiful.
I also think it sounds beautiful.
Want to go to Ibiza?
I book the tickets today.
God will not ask whether we accept this life.
There is no choice.
Life is forced upon you.
You can only choose how you live it.
Or not, that's also a choice.
A cup of tea can solve everything.
Sick? Tea.
Did you leave your husband? Tea is the solution.
Damn, Frances.
What have you done?
For as you thought, "Frances probably still alive,
otherwise they can not tell you this. "
Now you know so.
But I was finally free.
God finally gave me a lucky break.
Where is she?
In her bedroom.
That afternoon Reggie drank himself completely lamb.
What do you do differently,
if the only person you could get gone?
A cup of tea?
I did not think.
E? A big hat.
Sit down.
Do not stand there like a lamppost.
Move.
What is missing here? A bottle. Hurry up.
- Coming.
You wanted to see me, Ron?
- Indeed.
I want you to kill someone.
I'll give you ?1,000 for.
Leslie.
That is 500, the half.
You get the rest when it happened.
You can not count, but everything is there.
You can do it in your pocket.
It's for you.
Put the damn in your pocket.
We know you have no money.
Do not be so stupid.
Who is it?
Mom, wait here.
Stop, Mom.
- You killed her.
You killed my daughter, asshole.
?100 per week to spend flowers,
does not bring her back. Killer.
You'll rot in hell, Reggie Kray.
McVitie, what are you doing here?
I have a message from Ron for you.
Away.
I'll send an attorney,
or who have already arranged?
I want security
my wife and children is guaranteed.
Payne.
He gave everything.
Names, dates, times.
Documents, everything.
All the pieces will fit together ...
and they have a dozen witnesses
they protect.
Nipper ...
Nipper, what?
He retrieved the barmaid again.
She does not get out.
Where's Ron?
This song is part of me.
Great song.
It's your favorite.
Opzouten, sentimental dick.
What?
He still goes through, Ian.
- Do not start him.
Opzouten.
- Well, thanks for asking.
Be a little happier, my friend.
It is almost Christmas.
Why do not you dance?
Why would you come to a party,
if you are not going to entertain yourself?
I'm waiting for Jack the Hat.
What does he do now?
He swings with his gun clubs?
What did you think going after Leslie Payne,
would bring us?
What was I thinking?
- You heard me.
If you do not know,
I do not have to justify myself to you.
There he is.
Ron, let's see how.
Hello, where are the women?
- Jack the Hat.
Mr. Bender, how is it?
Good to see you.
Esther?
- Jackie.
I should never have let you go,
that was a mistake.
I'm going to get a drink.
When I return, I'll tell you why.
Ron.
Teddy.
Look, Ron. Jack is there.
- What is it?
A cigarette, Jack.
- I just stopped.
Would you lost something, Reg?
About you.
Leslie Payne?
What were you thinking?
You ruined it.
I do not know what you're talking about.
- Do not lie to me.
I let myself if not treated.
- What do you want, Jack?
Shut up.
- He will not help you.
You're not right in the head.
Review what happened to Frances
not at me.
What did you say?
It's not my fault that Frances suicide
committed. The pills did she not mine.
Are you joking?
- Reggie.
Shoot him.
Say that again.
- Reggie.
Say her name. I challenge you.
Frances.
Why did you do that?
Because I can not murder you,
how much I want too.
Reggie?
Reg, look at me.
What happened to you on?
You kill a man in a room full of people.
Are you crazy?
What?
Reggie once said that the center of the world
could be anywhere.
Even here, in the east of London.
The world looks like London.
Not good or bad, but it just exists.
There is no morality or shame,
only your own, solitary rules ...
until your life is over.
Until the end.
So we're just ghosts
of the people we once were.
Reggie had to sit 33 years
for the murder of Jack McVitie.
All these years, to the end,
He had a pair of tickets with him.
Reggie, my prince.
I thought we were going to Ibiza.
Reggie Kray was released eight weeks before he
died of cancer on 01-10-2000. He was 66.
Ronald Kray was found guilty
for the murder of George Cornell.
He was declared insane
and stayed at the Broadmoor psychiatric ...
until he died of a heart attack on 17-03-1995.
www.moviesubtitles.org